Fearing is believing.
The Skeleton Key is a drama, horror, mystery film directed by Iain Softley.
A hospice nurse working at a spooky New Orleans plantation home finds
herself entangled in a mystery involving the house's dark past.
Caroline Ellis, played by Kate Hudson.
Violet Devereaux, played by Gena Rowlands.
Luke Marshall, played by Peter Sarsgaard.
Ben Devereaux, played by John Hurt.
Jill, played by Joy Bryant.
Bayou Woman, played by Marion Zinser.
The Skeleton Key is a 2005 American supernatural folk horror film directed by Iain Softley and
starring Kate Hudson, Gena Rowlands, John Hurt, Peter Sarsgaard, and Joy Bryant.
The screenplay by Ehren Kruger follows a New Orleans hospice nurse who begins a job at a Terrebonne Parish plantation home, and
becomes entangled in a mystery involving the house, its former inhabitants, and Hoodoo rites that took place there.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and grossed
$94 million on a budget of $43 million.
The film explores themes of dreams, nurse, key,
new orleans, louisiana, plantation.
The tone is intense and mind_bending and dark.